we can't do much about some of the
external risks you know inflation and
stuff like that we cannot protect
business strategy we cannot do much
about right so uh so those things are
outside but if you look at the things
that is in our control the approach that
we've taken as an as a company is that
can we go down to the details of what is
the risk that you have and is there a
mitigation that we can do through maybe
process change maybe part you know you
know process you know maybe uh designing
your flows better maybe some tools to
you know prevent an event from happening
use of Technology Solutions I'll give
you a couple of examples
[Music]
so one of the things that we do we have
the specialist risk Engineers who go and
evaluate the factory not from an
underwriting perspective but evaluating
it from the risk perspective what is the
fire hazard and can we do something
about you know maybe changing a broad
layout people are at times very casual
about keeping incredible stuff lying
around so can we give those rehabilities
we then track those recommendations with
those corporates whether they actually
Implement obviously we give maybe 100
recommendations medicines some of them
will be easy to implement low cost
we prioritize those customers will be
willing to do that our experience is
that over the let's say last year we
have worked with 3000 plus companies
large new game small
of all the recommendations that we've
given see 62 percent of the
recommendations have actually been
implemented by the government so they're
seeing some value
then build some you know use of The
Cutting Edge tools so I'll give you
another example so you have a fire
hydrating system every company has a
nice you know printed red fire hydrant
system
what we realized that at times those
water pressure in the 500 system may be
eradicated for fire happens
so you know we have iot devices that
track the water pressure in the fire
hydrating system so the factory manager
will know that if there's a drop if
something is wrong with the internal
maybe something wrong with the with the
with the with a valve or something out
of the pump you can you can correct it
in textile factories what we've seen is
fire risk happens because of uh you know
it's it's there's a tendency to self you
know the the fire to start by itself so
if you maintain humidity at a certain
level the probability of that risk comes
down so you have sensors humidity
sensors that you're given to some of our
corporates to ensure that the level of
humidity is adequate so we bring down
the probability of a fire hazard just
give you the few examples there are many
such examples I don't want to take all
your time talking about this again
thank you